{
    "subject": "resource/Newton_Running",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Manufacturer",
    "human_readable": "Newton Running is a Manufacturer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9257550239562988,
            "question": "What kind of company is Newton Running?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8447287678718567,
            "question": "What industry is Newton Running in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8085760474205017,
            "question": "Is Newton Running a producer of goods?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7924733757972717,
            "question": "What products does Newton Running make?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7346451878547668,
            "question": "Who are the customers of Newton Running?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7208923697471619,
            "question": "How are Newton Running's products made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6448057889938354,
            "question": "What does Newton Running do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5737525224685669,
            "question": "Where might you find Newton Running products?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.536794900894165,
            "question": "What is the purpose of Newton Running?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4648335874080658,
            "question": "Does Newton Running have a website?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Newton Running is a Manufacturer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4695_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the purpose of Newton Running?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4695_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might you find Newton Running products?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4695_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does Newton Running do?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4695_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4695_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4695_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4695_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4695_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4695_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4695_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4695_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4695_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4695_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4695_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of whether the statement \"Newton Running is a manufacturer\" is supported by the documents:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because all four documents mention that Newton Running is involved in designing and manufacturing running shoes, which suggests that they are indeed manufacturers."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain multiple mentions of Newton Running as a brand that specializes in designing and manufacturing running shoes, which supports the statement that \"Newton Running is a Manufacturer.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}